At ease, soldier.
稍息 士兵
Go around, you jerk.
你不会超车啊 蠢货！
That's no road rage.
这不是普通的暴走族
Someone's trying to bump me off.
有人想撞死我…
Prime?
…擎天柱？
Prime, have you flipped your metal wig?
擎天柱！你的铁头生锈了？
- Haha... - Yes!
哈哈 很好！
Go! Go! Go!
快点！快点！快点！
Metal to the pedal, Miko.
全速前进 神子
Go, Jack, go!
快开 杰克 快开！
No way! Raf's scorching us.
不可能！拉夫完胜我们了！
Prime? Do you read me?
擎天柱？听到了吗？
I'm sorry, Agent Fowler.
我很抱歉 福特探员
Optimus isn't here at the moment.
擎天柱此刻正好不在
Then I'll take that asa confirmation
那么这正好说明
that he's presently trying to run me off the road!
想把我撞飞的就是他
Agent Fowler, that hardly seems likely.
福勒探员 这不太可能
Tell that to my burning treads!
这话你跟我快烧焦的轮胎说吧！
Come on. Come on...
快！快点！
Prime, no!
擎天柱！不要！
Looks like Optimus.
看着是挺像擎天柱
Primes don't run.
领袖们才不会逃跑
You all right in there?
你还好吗？
At ease, soldier.
稍息 士兵
Yes, that's it. Follow the light.
很好 就这样 跟着这道光
Wait. What?
啊 等等 什么？
Not the best choice of words, Ratchet.
你这样说吓死我了 救护车
Arcee, are you all right?
阿尔茜 你还好吗？
Sure. Except for being blindsided by Optimus.
当然 除了被擎天柱偷袭了一下
Didn't I tell you?
我没骗你们吧！？
Impossible.
难以置信！
I'm only reporting what I saw.
我只是在汇报我的所见所闻
Why would Optimus try to knock off Agent Fowler?
擎天柱为什么要撞死福勒探员？
Maybe Optimus believes he's a Decepticon all over again.
嗯 或许擎天柱又认为自己是霸天虎了
Or he's been faking being a good guy all this time.
或者他这段时间只是假装好人！
If Prime has gone off the rails for any reason,
不管擎天柱为了何种理由而行为越轨
we have a serious problem.
我们都有麻烦了
This is absurd.
太荒谬了！
A quick check for Optimus' signal will reveal
对擎天柱的信号监测表明
that he's nowhere near the location of tonight's incident.
他今晚压根不在事发现场
In fact, he's just returning now.
事实上 他正要返回基地
Is something wrong?
出什么事了吗？
We were just...
我们只是…
wondering where you've been.
…想知道你去哪儿了？
We haven't been able to reach you.
我们无法联系上你
I have been outside of our communication range...
我的位置超出了我们的通讯范围
- Whoa. - Easy.
- 哇哦！ - 别冲动！
... in a subterranean Energon deposit.
在一个地下能量矿中
Come on. It's our guy. Can't you tell?
得了吧 他是自己人 不是吗？
We're... sorry.
我们…很抱歉
Don't blame them, Prime.
不要责备他们 擎天柱
I was attacked earlier tonight,
今晚早些时候 我被袭击了
out on the open highway by a big rig--
某人将我撞出了高速公路
one that bore a striking resemblance to you.
而它与你惊人地相似
Halt!
停下！
This is a restricted area.
这里是军事禁区
Exit the vehicle, or we will open fire.
立刻下车 否则我们开火了！
I am Optimus Prime, leader of the autobots.
我是擎天柱 汽车人的首领
And I bring you this message.
我来向你们传达一个信息
Fowler.
我是福勒
What?!
什么？
That's not possible.
那不可能！
I can tell you sure as there are 50 stars on my star-spangled shorts
我以我短裤上的五十个星星打赌
it isn't him!
那不是他！
Alden military base is under attack... by Optimus Prime.
奥列尼军事基地被擎天柱袭击了！
The truck?
那个卡车？
The 'Bot.
机器人！
Fire! Fire!
开火！开火！
There. They brought reinforcements. Resume fire!
在那儿！他搬来了援军！继续开火！
Autobots, return to base.
汽车人 返回基地
We must not inflict human casualties.
我们必须避免伤及人类
No, General Bryce.
不 布莱斯将军
Optimus Prime did not attack our boys.
擎天柱没有攻击我们的人
Because I was with Prime when I received the alert.
当我收到警报时 擎天柱就站在我身边！
Yes, sir. The Autobots were at your base,
是的 长官 汽车人去了你的基地
but only in response to the initial attack.
但那只是为了应对刚才的袭击
But, sir, I... Yes, sir. I understand.
但是 长官 我…是的 长官 我明白了
So, what's the damage?
这次损失有多大？
All military personnel are under strict orders
所有军队进入一级戒备
to destroy any and all 'Bots on sight.
对所有的机器人 格杀勿论
Are you kidding?!
你开玩笑吗？
But th-they're innocent.
他们是无辜的
Optimus was framed!
擎天柱被陷害了！
Though unfortunate,
这很不幸
the military order changes nothing.
但是这种命令不能解决问题
Our imposter clearly poses a grave threat to humanity.
那个冒牌货显然给人类造成了巨大的威胁
A 30-foot-tall transforming imposter.
一个三十英尺高的变形冒牌货
They actually did it.
他们真的完成了
Those butchers managed to crack the code.
那些屠夫设法破译了代码
M.E.C.H.
机械党
Sir, any parallax or latency issues?
长官 有视差或其他潜在问题吗？
The telepresence interface performed flawlessly
不管是汽车还是机器人形态
in vehicular and robot mode.
远程操控界面都非常地完美
M.E.C.H. abducted Breakdown...
机械党劫持了打击
and by all indications deconstructed him from cranial chamber to heel strut.
他们把他从头到脚都拆了个遍
I was there.
我亲眼所见
And we know that, more recently,
而且我们最近得知
they obtained Starscream's T-cog.
他们获得了红蜘蛛的变形齿轮
Which they evidently installed in a knockoff of you.
显然 他们将它安在了冒牌货身上
Which, in turn, scanned an appropriate vehicle form.
使他能扫描一个合适的车型
Fill the tank with Energon...
再填满能量仓
... and say hello to Nemesis Prime.
然后黑暗擎天柱就诞生了！
So, where do we start?
我们要从哪儿开始？
M.E.C.H.'s base could be anywhere.
我们根本不知道机械党在哪儿
Not necessarily.
别担心
While M.E.C.H. may have learned much of our biology...
尽管机械党了解了我们的生理构造
They haven't necessarily absorbed our technology.
但他们还没有完全掌握我们的技术
Without access to a Ground Bridge,
没有我们的环陆桥
Nemesis Prime would rely solely on its vehicle mode for transportation.
黑暗擎天柱只能靠车轮子来回奔波
Chances are the M.E.C.H. base is within driving distance of both incidents.
机械党的据点很可能就在两个事故现场的行车范围以内
What are we waiting for?
那我们还等什么？
Let's get out there and mash M.E.C.H's little science project.
去把机械党的小小科技项目砸个稀巴烂吧！
Agent Fowler, I do not think it advisable to put yourself
福勒探员 我不建议你再次置身于
in harm's way of M.E.C.H's robot again.
机械党的机器人所带来的危险之中
Well, I'm not sure it's advisable for 'Bots to be running recon with the military out there gunning for you.
好吧 我也不建议汽车人 再次跑出去当军队的靶子
We will maintain vehicular cover until absolutely necessary.
我们会保持汽车形态 除非发生紧急情况
Nothing but tumbleweeds.
除了杂草什么都没有
Just a whole lot of empty.
一片空旷
Bumblebee, proceed with utmost caution.
大黄蜂 你要加倍小心
Reconnaissance only. We will rendezvous at your coordinates.
只许侦查 不许交战 我们会在指定地点与你会合
The Autobots are persistent.
顽固不化的汽车人
Time to meet their match.
他们的对手该登场了
Bumblebee.
大黄蜂
Be on your guard.
保持警惕
My double could be anywhere.
冒牌货随时可能出现…
I'm sorry. What?
…抱歉 你说什么？
Bumblebee. Do you read?
大黄蜂 收到了吗？
Fan out?
散开？
And beware of anything that might resemble me.
小心任何跟我相似的东西
If I can isolate the control frequency of the remote link Silas is employing,
如果我能分离出塞拉斯的遥控信号
I should be able to pinpoint his exact position.
我就能精确定位出他的位置
Remote link?
遥控？
You didn't think M.E.C.H. possessed the ability
难道你觉得机械党有高超的技术
to build a completely autonomous robot, did you?
去制造一个有自我意识的机器人吗？
I was hoping Silas would be operating the 'Bot from inside
我倒希望塞拉斯正躲在内部进行控制
because one punch from Bulkhead, and booyah!
这样隔板一拳下去就可以 呼呀！
Aha! Frequency isolated.
啊哈！信号锁定！
Then reopen that bridge.
那就打开环陆桥
Agent Fowler, did you not hear Optimus advise against your involvement?
福勒探员 你没听到擎天柱拒绝你参与进来吗？
It's for your own safety.
这关系到你的安全！
Look, doc, I don't plan on dancing with any 'Bots,
听着 医生 我没打算和机器人打架
but there's a human element in play here,
但是那里有人类参与其中
and in case you haven't noticed,
也许你还不知道
I happen to be a highly trained, government-grade, human.
我是一名受过特殊训练的 政府级别的 人类
Yeah. Plus Silas tried to run him off the road, It's personal.
没错 塞拉斯曾想把他撞飞 这是私人恩怨
Optimus Prime. We meet again.
擎天柱 我们又见面了
The deception ends here, Silas.
你的骗局到此为止了 塞拉斯
Does it?
是这样吗？
I think I'm gonna toss the breakfast I ate back in flight school.
我连在飞行学校吃的早餐都要吐出来了
Agent Fowler, the control frequency is transmitting
福勒探员 遥控信号的发射源
from a structure 100 meters due north.
在正北100米处的建筑中
Copy that.
收到了
My robot chassis possesses all your strength, speed, and firepower.
我的机器人完全复制了你的力量 速度还有火力
Add my extensive combat training,
并且融入了我的格斗技艺
and M.E.C.H. has clearly achieved the perfect meld of man and machine.
机械党已经将人类和机器完美地融合在一起
But the key difference between you and me?
知道你我之间的主要差异在哪儿吗？
My body can't feel pain!
我的身体感觉不到疼痛！
This is just the beginning.
这只是个开始
Imagine an army of transforming robots.
想象一下变形机器人组成的军队
No one will stand against the newly rebooted M.E.C.H.
没有人能对抗涅重生的机械党
Think again, Si.
再考虑下吧 小塞同志
Agent Fowler in the flesh at last.
福勒探员 你到底亲自出马了
And I'm pulling the plug on your video game.
我要拔掉你那游戏机的电源！
Ex-military?
你是军人出身？
Special tactics. You?
特种战术部队 你呢？
Army rangers.
游骑兵团
Retired, clearly.
很明显 已经退役了
I may be out of shape,
虽然有点儿发福
but I don't need to bust you up.
但我不需要打倒你！
I just need to buy Prime a little time.
我只是为擎天柱争取点时间
No. No!
不 不！
No! No! Nooo!
不 不 不！
Agent Fowler?
福勒探员？
That would be our boys.
那些是我们的人
I advise you to get back to base, Prime.
你最好返回基地 擎天柱
I'll handle Uncle Sam.
我来应付山姆大叔
So, how weird was it to see someone who looked exactly like Optimus
一个很像擎天柱的人把你打趴下了
kicking the scrap out of you?
这是多么诡异的一件事啊？
It's a sight I won't soon forget.
那个情景我永远也不会忘记
The question remains whether M.E.C.H. will continue to function as we know it... without its leader.
不知道失去了领导人 机械党是否还会一如既往地继续行动
Well, here's the kicker.
还里有一个坏消息
We sifted through the wreckage with a fine-tooth comb...
我们仔细地检查过了
And couldn't find any trace of Silas.
没有发现任何塞拉斯的踪迹
The internal damage to his organs is massive
他的内部脏器严重受损
and beyond the scope of conventional medicine.
常规的医疗水平已经无能为力
Fortunately for our leader,
但我们的领袖是幸运的
M.E.C.H. is anything but conventional.
因为机械党能打破常规